[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Warm and joyful spring season, spring flowers bloom, the
tiết xuân ấm áp vui tươi hoa xuân đua nở
earth and sky welcome spring. On the occasion of the New Year of the Rabbit
đất trời vào xuân Nhân dịp xuân mới Quý
2023, Tam Chieu Hoan Quan sends best
Mão 2023 tâm chiếu Hoàn quán xin gửi lời
wishes to all Dharma friends, children
chúc tới tất cả các quỹ đạo hữu các con
in the Youth Club, the
trong câu lạc bộ Tuổi Trẻ câu lạc bộ La
Rahula Club, and the entire Tam Xuan family.
Hầu La cùng toàn thể gia đình Tâm Xuân
May everything be as you wish, may wisdom and
hoan hỷ vạn sự như ý trí tuệ Khai Minh
enlightenment be diligently practiced, helping yourself and
chăm chuyên Phật pháp giúp mình giúp
others, bringing joy to the country. May
người tươi vui đất nước Chúc mong tất cả
we all have a happy and peaceful spring in the light of the
chúng ta năm mới trong ánh tử quang của
Ten Directions' Buddhas.
Mười Phương Chư Phật vui xuân an lạc
[Music] Pink
[âm nhạc]
rays of sunlight gently drift across the sky, creating poetry. Flowers bloom playfully, bees and
tia nắng hồng bồng bềnh mấy nhẹ trôi
butterflies
ngang trời thành thơ Hoa đùa nở ong bướm
happily fly and frolic in the spring. The enlightened ones shine
vui rộn ràng bay nô đùa mùa xuân
brighter than a thousand suns, spreading
bậc chi giác sáng hơn ngàn ánh dương tỏa
fragrance throughout the ten directions, saving sentient beings.
hương khắp mười phương cứu độ chúng sinh
Buddha Shakyamuni. The Four Noble
Phật Thích Ca
Truths, humanity and heaven, when practiced, bring
Bốn chân lý nhân thiên thực hành được an
peace and happiness, fragrance spreading throughout the ten
lành hạnh phúc hương thơm khắp mười
directions. The Sunlight shines.
phương Ánh Dương tỏa
[Music]
[âm nhạc]